{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following statement is correct?", "opta": "A reference is stored on heap.", "optb": "A reference is stored on stack.", "optc": "A reference is stored in a queue.", "optd": "A reference is stored in a binary tree.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  Once a reference variable has been defined to refer to a particular variable it can refer to any other variable.\n  A reference is not a constant pointer.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Functions can be declared to return a reference type. There are reasons to make such a declaration/Which of the following reasons are correct?\n  The information being returned is a large enough object that returning a reference is more efficient than returning a copy. \n  The type of the function must be a R-value.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  Change a reference changes the referent.\n  We can create an array of references.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is correct about the references?", "opta": "A reference must always be initialized within functions.", "optb": "A reference must always be initialized outside all functions.", "optc": "A reference must always be initialized.", "optd": "Both A and C.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A reference is declared using the _____ symbol.", "opta": "&&", "optb": "&", "optc": "||", "optd": "!", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is correct?", "opta": "Once a reference variable has been defined to refer to a particular variable it can refer\nto any other variable.", "optb": "A reference is indicated by using && operator.", "optc": "Once a reference variable has been defined to refer to a particular variable it cannot refer to any other variable.", "optd": "A reference can be declared beforehand and initialized later.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  A reference is not a constant pointer.\n  A referenced is automatically de-referenced.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  An array of references is acceptable.\n  We can also create a reference to a reference.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is correct?", "opta": "A referenced has to be de-referenced to access a value.", "optb": "A referenced does not need to be de-referenced to access a value.", "optc": "A referenced has to be double de-referenced to access a value.", "optd": "Whether a reference should be de-referenced or not depends on the type of the reference.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  Once the variable and the reference are linked they are tied together.\n  Once the reference of a variable is declared another reference of that variable is not allowed.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  We can return a global variable by reference.\n  We cannot return a local variable by reference.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Reference is like a _____.", "opta": "Pointer", "optb": "Structure", "optc": "Macro", "optd": "Enum", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is correct?", "opta": "A reference is a constant pointer.", "optb": "A reference is not a constant pointer.", "optc": "An array of references is acceptable.", "optd": "It is possible to create a reference to a reference.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is correct?", "opta": "A reference is declared using * operator.", "optb": "Once a reference variable has been defined to refer to a particular variable it can refer to any other variable.", "optc": "A reference must always be initialized within classes.", "optd": "A variable can have multiple references.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statement is correct?", "opta": "An array of references is acceptable.", "optb": "Once a reference variable has been defined to refer to a particular variable it can refer to any other variable.", "optc": "An array of references is not acceptable.", "optd": "Reference is like a structure.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is correct?\n  Pointer to a reference and reference to a pointer both are valid.\n  When we use reference, we are actually referring to a referent.", "opta": "Only 1 is correct.", "optb": "Only 2 is correct.", "optc": "Both 1 and 2 are correct.", "optd": "Both 1 and 2 are incorrect.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}